Azizul Hakim

Computer Science Student



© CAREER OBJECTIVE

Third year Computer Science student seeking to use my academic knowledge in a fulltime position. Possess more than 2 year of handson experience building and testing programs in different languages like Java, C++, C and JavaScript. Also have the knowledge of computer hardware (adjusting, repairing and replacing parts). A motivated individual with strong communication skills and problemsolving skills.



EXPERIENCE

Banquet Server

Era Bistro and Catering, Winnipeg, MB / Jan 2018-Present

Delivering exceptional, fast and friendly customer service.

Server and Bartender

University of Manitoba Catering Services, Winnipeg, MB / Mar 2019–Present

Interacting with customers, taking orders and serving snacks and drinks.

Voluntary Math Tutor

Frontier College, Winnipeg, MB / Sep 2017-Apr 2018

Assisting kids from grades (1-8) with their homework.

Sustainability Ambassador

University of Manitoba, Winnipeg, MB / Sep 2019-present

Volunteer in many different sustainable events.

Certifications

Technical Support Fundamental

What I learned: Troubleshooting, Tech support, Operating systems.

What is Data Science?

What I learned: Data Science basics, Data Science tools.

Facial Expression Recognition with Keras

What I learned: Deep learning, Machine learning, Neural networks.

Logistic Regression with NumPy and Python

What I learned: Data Science, Machine learning, Python, NumPy.

KPMG Data Analytics Consulting Virtual Internship (ongoing)

What I'm learning: Data quality assessment, Data analytics, Data insights and presentation.



CONTACT

Email:

koushikrakib@gmail.com

Phone:

2048991451

Address:

134-150 Baylor Avenue, Winnipeg, MB

Linkedin:

linkedin.com/in/azizul-hakim-41862b1a2/

Github:

github.com/AzizulHakim96



Connect4 game in Java

Online ordering System

Budget Balancing App

Personal Website



HARD SKILLS

Java, C, C++, SQL,

JavaScript, Python, HTML,

CSS, Linux, Lc-3 Assembly,

Microsoft Office, Aws,

Data Entry



EDUCATION

B.S. / COMPUTER

SCIENCE University of Manitoba, Winnipeg,

Manitoba 2017-2022